Kaizhi Du

Personal Website: http://dukaizhi.herokuapp.com/ | Email: http://dukaizhi.herokuapp.com/ | Email: https://www.linkedin.com/in/kaizhi-du-1588a8181/

SUMMARY

❖ To obtain a work position as software developer

Master student in Information Technology, dedicated to learning in the Software Development field. I have nearly three years of software development experience, proficient in multiple software technologies.

SKILLS

Proficient: React, Redux, Redux-form, Redux-thunk, RestfulAPI, jQuery, Ajax, Express, Mongoose, Spring, Mybatis

Skilled: Redux-saga, GraphQL, AWS API Gateway, AWS Lambda, AWS DynamoDB

EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer (Internship), Online Course System, Tap series, CA

4/2019 - 9/2019

- Used React to design create online course, and add features such as loading courses
- Used python to convert all xml files into json files.

Software Engineer, *University Management System*, Chaoxing, China

2/2017 - 3/2018

- > Used JavaScript, jQuery, Ajax and other technologies to build the front-end page of the student course selection system.
- Work with colleagues to develop student graduation modules. I am responsible for setting the basic data for graduation and confirming graduation.
- Used POI to export various types of schedules, student schedules, teacher schedules, classroom schedules, etc.

Designer and Developer (freelance), Mechanical ERP System

2/2017 - NOW

- > Designed the Architecture of the entire system
- ➤ Used technologies such as JavaScript, jQuery, ajax as front-end. Java, Spring, Mybatis, MySql as back-end.
- ➤ The entire system implements functions such as allocating daily work, cash flow management, warehouses management, exporting excel reports, and generating production progress charts.

Software Engineer (Internship), Enterprise Tax System, Inspur, China

9/2016 – 1/2017

- Learned software programming, familiar with the use of Tomcat, Spring, MySQL and, etc.
- Used Spring to integrate the information of small and medium enterprises in government departments.

EDUCATION

California Lutheran University, Thousand Oaks, CA	9/2018 – 5/2020
Master of Information Technology	
ChangChun University of Technology, ChangChun, China	9/2012 – 6/2016
Bachelor of Computer Science	